Guide to the Bruce Voeller papers, 1956-1990
Voeller, Bruce papers, 1956-1990
- Series I. Subject Files and Correspondence
  - General Subject And Correspondence Files
    - Gay Rights National Lobby (GRNL) (Box 35, Folder 11-12)
    - GAF Corporation (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Gaffney, Morgan (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - "Gay" - Use of the Word (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Gay Health and Practices (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Gay History (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Gay and Lesbian Community Service Center (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Gays in the Military (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Gay Ol' Times (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Gays (Older) Reminiscences (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Gay Parents (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Gay Producers Associations (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Gay Report on STDs (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Gays - Rich (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - General Information (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Gilmour, John (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Glazier, Henry (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Gould, R. (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Gonorrhea (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Goodstein, David (Box 35, Folder 31-36)
    - "H" Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Human Rights Campaign Fund (Box 35, Folder 38-39)
    - Harris, Virginia (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Helfcott, M. (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Hepatitis A (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - Hepatitis B (Box 35, Folder 43-44)
    - Hepatitis C (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Herpes (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - F - H (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Hoffmann, Beverly - The National Deferred Giving Trust (Box 36, Folder 1-4)
    - Holocaust (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Homosexuality/Homosexuals (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
      - Homosexuals and Hormones (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Incidence (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Origin (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Sex-Chromosome (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Hooker, E., See also audiocassette: Bruce Voeller and Evelyn Hooker, April 23, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 12-13)
    - Hormel (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Hustler (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Hydroxythyl Cellulose (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - "I" Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - IBM (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - International Planned Parenthood Federation (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Insurance (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Isherwood, Chris (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Islander's Club Blue Flettrich (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - "J" Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Jackson, M. (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - JICK (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Johnson and Johnson (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - "K" Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Kameny (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Kaiser-Permanente Dr. Petti (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - King, Billie Jean (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Kinsey, Alfred (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Kinsey Review (Box 36, Folder 32-35)
    - Kirkpatrick, M. (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Kline (Box 36, Folder 37-38)
    - Kreiss (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - "L" Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Levy, J. (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Lies/Truth (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Lists (Box 36, Folder 43-45)
    - H - L (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Lists (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
    - Los Angeles Times (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Locke (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Lowenstein, Al (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Lubraseptic (Box 37, Folder 6-8)
    - "M" Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Man's World (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Marcus, Steve (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Masters (Box 37, Folder 12-14)
    - Mariposa - Advertisements/Articles (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Benefits (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Brochures (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Council of Overseers (Box 37, Folder 18-20)
      - Endowment (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - 50 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Fundraising (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - Institutional Review Board (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Mailings (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - Memorabilia (Box 37, Folder 26)
      - Newsletter (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - Portraits (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Press Release (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Matek, Stan (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - McWhirter - Mattison (Box 37, Folder 31-32)
    - Menfegol (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Meridian (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Merrill Lynch (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Milk - Ovulation (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Miller, Joe (Box 37, Folder 37-39)
    - Mormons (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - "N" Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - NAMBLA (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - National Gay Health Education Foundation (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - National Gay Rights Advocates (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - National Coalition of Gay STD Services (Box 37, Folder 46-49)
    - Nevada (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - New York Native (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Nobel Prize (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Nobile, Philip (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Nonoxynol-9 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Novelists (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - "O" Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Optimation (Box 38, Folder 8-10)
      - Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 11-12)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - 1982-1984 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 15-16)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 18-19)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 20-21)
      - 1990 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - 1991 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - 1992 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - 1993 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - 1994 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Oral Sex (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Originals (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Ostrow, David (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - "P" Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Pain (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Papilloma (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Peacock, R. (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Penis (Box 38, Folder 36-39)
    - N - P (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Planned Parenthood Convention (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Police (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Population Council (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Population Information (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Pornography (Box 39, Folder 5-6)
    - Post Office Bulk (Box 39, Folder 7-9)
    - Post Office (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Potts (Box 39, Folder 11-12)
    - Pratt (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Press (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Press, Gay (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Projects (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Prostitutes (Box 39, Folder 17-18)
    - Prudential - Bache (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Quakers (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - "R" Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Rape (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Referenda (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Roth, Michael (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Russell, David (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - "S" Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Society for Scientific Study of Sex (SSSS) (Box 39, Folder 27-29)
    - STDs (Box 39, Folder 30-32)
    - Savin Corporation (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Schulte, Steve (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Security Clearance (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Segal (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Semen (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Serex International (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Sex (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Sex Determination (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Sex Orientation/Hormone (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Sexual Behavior (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - Shanti (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - SIECUS (Sex Information and Education Council of the U.S.) (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - Signatures (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - Small, Bill (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - Socrides (Socoraides?) (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - Sodomy (Box 39, Folder 48)
    - Spellman (Box 39, Folder 49)
    - Sponge (Box 39, Folder 50)
    - Statistics - Handling of (Box 39, Folder 51)
    - Stevens, Cladd (Box 39, Folder 52)
    - Stephens, Frank (Box 39, Folder 53)
    - P - S (Box 39, Folder 54)
    - H.R. 166, 1975 Gay Rights Bill, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Bruce Voeller: "My Days on the Task Force", 1979 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Bruce Voeller Broadside: "Homosexuality: The Last Debate" (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Bruce Voeller: Gay Rights National Lobby, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Bruce Voeller Professional Involvements (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - C.A. Tripp: reviewers' comments, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Codebook, Kinsey Data (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - AIDS Research, 1986-1988 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - AIDS Articles, 1987-1990 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - AIDS Research and Politics-Articles and Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - AIDS Articles and Correspondence, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - AIDS Research, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - AIDS Research and Politics-Articles and Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - AIDS Research, 1989-1990 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - "Women and AIDS: Promoting Healthy Behaviors" (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - California AIDS Politics, 1988-1990 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - AIDS Treatments-Articles, Press Releases (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Bruce Voeller Correspondence: AIDS Treatment (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Bruce Voeller Article on Condom Research, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Bruce Voeller Condom Research Results (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - FDA on Female Condoms (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - AIDS Transmission Research (Box 40, Folder 22-24)
    - Heterosexual Transmission, 1987-1990 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Optimation (Box 41, Folder 1-7)
    - Tripp (Box 41, Folder 8-10)
    - Bruce Voeller Letters, 1979-1985 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence from Various Groups (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Articles, 1973-1990 (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
    - Book Feeding, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Brown, Howard, 1941-1975 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Council of Planning Affiliates - "Report of the Taskforce of Sexual Minorities", 1977 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Freud (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Gay Activists Alliance - New York City, 1972-1976 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Gay Movement, 1973-1990 (Box 53, Folder 8-17)
    - Gay Movement - Articles, Brochures, etc., 1973-1990 (Box 53, Folder 18-19)
    - Gay Movement - Articles, Fliers, Pamphlets, Some Correspondence, 1973-1990 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Gays (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Health Problems (Clippings, etc.), 1972-1977 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Leaflets, 1973-1990 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Magazine and Programs Signed By People, 1973-1987 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Masters and Johnson (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings, Correspondence, Etc., 1973-1990 (Box 53, Folder 26-27)
    - Advocate, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Anderson/Voeller - Final Chapter, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Condoms/AIDS British Medical Journal, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Condom/N-9 Letter, Village Voice, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Congress, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Contraception, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Dungeon Master, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - "Exposed to Virus" The Lancet, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - International Conference on AIDS - Atlanta, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Journal of the American Medical Association (JAMA), AIDS/Condom Break, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Journal of the American Medical Association - Anorectal Cancer, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Journal of the American Medical Association - Heterosexual Anal Sex, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Journal of the American Medical Association - SMOG/Condoms, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Kinsey Symposium, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - The Lancet, HTLV-III and Saliva, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - The Lancet, N-9 and AIDS Virus, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - The Lancet, N-9 and HIV, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Lubricants, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 18-19)
    - Manuscript - Conrad, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Manuscript - Conrad, 1989-1990 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Memoirs - Homosexual Behavior, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Voeller Writings, 1963-1991 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - New York Native, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 24-25)
    - N-9 HIV, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - N-9 and Sexually Transmitted Diseases, Paris Conference, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - "The Problems of Gay Youth" by Bruce Voeller (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - "Promiscuous" New England Journal of Medicine, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Voeller Articles pre-1980 - Includes "Little Italy" and "Gay Fathers" (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Voeller Articles, Christopher Street, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Voeller Reprints, 1963-1964 (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - Voeller with Livengood, Allison, American Journal of OBGYN, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - Voeller Writings, 1952-1983 (Box 55, Folder 34)
    - N-9 HIV, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 35)
    - Bruce Voeller Miscellaneous (Box 55, Folder 36-38)
    - Voeller Obituaries, Cards, Personal (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Voeller C.V. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Personal Photos (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Voeller Personal (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 57)
    - Photographs (family?) (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Voeller, Bruce: "My Days on the Task Force", 1979 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Voeller, B. "Society and the Gay Movement", 1980 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Voeller, B. Publications (STDs, AIDS, homosexuality, anal sex), 1983-1992 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Voeller, B. Integrated Behavioral and Biomedical Approach to AIDS, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Voeller, B-- Mariposa Occasional Papers articles, 1983-1993 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Voeller, B--Interview with Forum, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - AIDS, See also audiocassette: Plenary-AIDS: Update and Prevention, Mckusick, Voeller, Wyatt
    - Advertising (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - AIDS: Abuses (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - AIDS: Africa (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
    - Aging, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - AIDS: Anthropology, 1990-1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - AIDS: Bibliographies (Bruce Voeller) (Box 12, Folder 7-9)
    - AIDS Commission, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 10-11)
    - AIDS Foundations, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - AIDS Nursing Update, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - AIDS Project Los Angeles, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - AIDS Publications, 1982-1985 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - AIDS Record, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - ALPHA (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - American Association of Physicians for Human Rights (AAPHR) (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Alexander, Nancy (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - AMFAR (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Anal Sex (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Antibodies (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Antibody Test (Box 12, Folder 23-25)
    - Antigens (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - ARC (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Artificial Insemination (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Asia (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Asymptomatic HIV+, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Australia (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - B2 Micro-Globulin, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Baths (Box 12, Folder 33-35)
    - Bay Area Physicians for Human Rights (BAPHR) (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Behavior Modification (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Belle Glade (Mosquitoes), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Bisexuality (Box 12, Folder 39-40)
    - Blood (Box 12, Folder 41-42)
    - Blood Commission Report (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Books (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Brain, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Brandt, Edward (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Brazil (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Britain (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - AIDS Medical Update (Gay Men's Health Crisis Letter), 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - CAIN (Computer AIDS Info Network) (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - California, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Cameron, Paul, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Canada, 1984-1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Carrier State, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Cases, #, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Casual Contact, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Cause, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - CD4 (Lymphocytes) (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - CD4 without Viremia (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - CD4 V.D. Data (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - CDC (Center for Disease Control) (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Cells, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Circumcision, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Civil Rights, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Clergy, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Co-factors, 1985-1989 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Confidentiality (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Coolfont Report, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Costs/Medical Costs, 1986-1991 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Crenshaw (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Curran, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Current AIDS Literature, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Cyr, Howard, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Decker, Bruce, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Decontamination (Box 13, Folder 26-27)
    - Definitions (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Dental (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Diagnosis, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Discrimination--Insurance (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Discrimination-Miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Disease Progression (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Drug Users/I.V. Drugs/I.V. (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Duesberg, Peter (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Early Cases (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Early Detection (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Education (Box 13, Folder 38-40)
    - Epidemiology (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Ethical Issues (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Europe (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Exposed to the Virus (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Family (Organizational Meeting of National Coalition on AIDS and the Family), 1987 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Feline AIDS, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Female to Male to Female Transmission (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Fraud (Box 13, Folder 48-49)
    - Funds, 1987-1992 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Gallo (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC) (Box 13, Folder 52-53)
    - Genetics (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Genital Ulcers (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Germany (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Gloves, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Gonorrhea, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Gottlieb, Michael (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Government (Box 13, Folder 60-62)
      - California (Box 13, Folder 63-64)
      - Federal (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
      - Federal Hearings, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Federal Hearings, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Federal Hearings, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - New York, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Vasconcellos (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
    - GUD (Genital Ulcerative Disease) (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Health Care Workers (Box 14, Folder 11-12)
    - Hemophilia (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Heterosexuals (Box 14, Folder 14-15)
    - Hicks, Don, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - HIV Virus (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - HIV-2 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Homosexual, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Hospitalization, 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Houston, KS/AIDS Foundation of, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Hyperthermia, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Immune Changes (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Inactivation of Virus (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Incidence (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Incubation Period (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Indiana AIDS Report, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Infectious Dose (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Infectious Route (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Inoculation, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Insurance, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - International AIDS Conference I, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - International AIDS Conference III, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - International AIDS Society, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - IVDU (Intravenous Drug Users) (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Kaposi's Sarcoma (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - KOOP (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Kramer, Larry (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Krim, Mathilde (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - L.A. Cares, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - La Rouche, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Latency (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Latin America (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Legal--Law, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Legal-Law (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Legislation (Box 15, Folder 7-8)
    - Lesbian and Gay Health (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - LeVay, Simon, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Lifelines, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Los Angeles (Box 15, Folder 12-14)
    - Lymphocytes (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Mayor's/Supervisor's Commission (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - MACS (Multi-Center AIDS Cohort Project), 1987 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Mechanism/Blood of HIV Infected (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Medical (Box 15, Folder 19-24)
    - Meetings/Conferences - National Meetings (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Meetings/Conferences (Box 15, Folder 26-27)
    - Meetings/Conferences-Hawaii, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Meetings/Conferences-Kaposi, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Meta-Analysis (MAP), 1993 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Military (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Milk (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Minorities, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 34-35)
    - MMWR (Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Reports), 1981-1985 (Box 15, Folder 36)
      - MMWR, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 37)
      - MMWR, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 38)
      - MMWR, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 39)
      - MMWR, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 40)
      - MMWR, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 41)
      - MMWR, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - MMWR, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
    - Medical (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Models (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - National Commission (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - NGHEF (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - NIH (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Nitrites (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Nutrition (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Opportunistic Infections (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Oral Sex (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Organizations (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Origin (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Osborne, June (Box 16, Folder 15-16)
    - Padian, Nancy (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Pamphlets (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Pamphlets (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Papilloma Virus (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Parasites (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Partner-Notification (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Pearce, Richard (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Pediatrics/Perinatal (Box 16, Folder 23-24)
    - Person with AIDS (PWA) (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Pittsburgh (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Policy (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Politics (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Politics (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Polls (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Predictions (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Press (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Prevention (Box 16, Folder 32-33)
    - Prisons (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Prognosis (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Progression (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - "Promiscuous" (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Prostitution (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Psychology/Neurology/Brain/CNS (Box 16, Folder 39-41)
    - Publications (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Quarantine (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Race (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Recruiting Subjects (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Relapse (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Religion (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Resources (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Reviews (Box 16, Folder 49-50)
    - Reviews (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
    - Risk Factors (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Risk Reduction (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
    - Russia, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - "Safe" Sex (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - SAIDS (Simian AIDS) (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Saliva, Tears, Urine, Milk, Vaginal Secretions (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - San Diego AIDS Project, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Schram, Neil (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Semen (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Sero (-) Viremia (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Sero (+) Viremia (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Sero (+) to ARC to AIDS (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Sero (+) Incidence, Incubation/Carrier (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Seroconversion (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Sex (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Shanti (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Siecus Report, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Siecus Report, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Sleep (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Spread (Transmission/Infectivity) (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Statistics (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Survival, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Swine Fever, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Syphilis (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - T-Cells/Lymphocytes (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Tears, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Television (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Test - Anti-body (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Testing (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Therapy
      - Acyclovir (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - AL721 (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Amphotericin (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - Ampligen (Box 17, Folder 36)
      - Atovaguone (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - AZT (Box 17, Folder 38-40)
      - B2 Microglobulin (Box 17, Folder 41)
      - Candidiasis (Box 17, Folder 42)
      - Cantharidin (Box 17, Folder 43)
      - CD4 (Box 17, Folder 44)